<resources>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">pointube</string>
    <string name="drawer_open" translatable="false">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="drawer_close" translatable="false">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <!-- 3 rules :
    1. This string resource file is grouped by screen page.
    For example, if string is founded in the login screen, then it must be placed under the comment "login"
    without concern if it is whether dialog, or toast (etc).

    2. When the string is used various places such as internet error message,
     it will be placed under comment "Utilities".

    3. If the string is used various places, but it's likely to change in the future based on screen,
     then it should be placed under its screen comment.  -->

    <!-- Zone 1 -->
    <!-- Screen -->

    <!-- Register Form -->
    <string name="register_form_text_account">ACCOUNT</string>
    <string name="register_form_text_your_profile">YOUR PROFILE</string>
    <string name="register_form_text_email">Email</string>
    <string name="register_form_text_password">Password</string>
    <string name="register_form_text_repeat_password">Confirm password</string>
    <string name="register_form_text_username">Username</string>
    <string name="register_form_text_first_name_en">First Name (En)</string>
    <string name="register_form_text_first_name_th">First Name (Th)</string>
    <string name="register_form_text_last_name_en">Last Name (En)</string>
    <string name="register_form_text_last_name_th">Last Name (Th)</string>
    <string name="register_form_text_dob">Date of Birth</string>
    <string name="register_form_text_hint_dob">Select date of birth</string>
    <string name="register_form_text_passport">Passport ID</string>
    <string name="register_form_text_citizen_id">Citizen ID</string>
    <string name="register_form_text_gender">Gender</string>
    <string name="register_form_text_gender_male">Male</string>
    <string name="register_form_text_gender_female">Female</string>
    <string name="register_form_text_change_password">Change Password</string>
    <string name="register_form_text_thai">Thai</string>
    <string name="register_form_text_expat">Expat</string>
    <string name="register_form_btn_register">Register</string>

    <string name="register_form_toast_register_successful">Register successful</string>
    <string name="register_form_dialog_progress_register_content">Registering</string>
    <string name="register_form_citizen_id_description">You must enter the citizen identification number exactly as it appears on the identification card.  Please re-check prior to submission.  You will not be able to correct the number once registered.  This is a part of the security measures to protect your personal information.</string>

    <!-- Terms and Condition -->
    <string name="terms_text_1">Last updated: May 18, 2016</string>
    <string name="terms_text_2">These Terms and Conditions of Service ("Terms of Service") govern your account on the Pointube mobile site
          (the "Pointube Sites" or the "Sites") and your use of the Sites and all products and services provided
          through the Pointube Sites. Pointube mobile site is operated by New Dimension CO., Ltd. ("Pointube", "we",
          or "our") and provides the content posted on the Sites subject to the following Terms of Service.</string>
    <string name="terms_text_3">These Terms of Service incorporate the entirety of the Pointube Privacy Policy posted on the Sites. Please
          read these Terms of Service carefully. By accessing and using the Sites, you agree to be bound by these
          Terms of Service. If you do not agree with these Terms of Service, please do not use the Pointube Sites.</string>
    <string name="terms_text_4">Pointube reserves the right to add to, delete, or change the Terms of Service at any time at its sole
          discretion, without notice. As such, you should check these Terms of Service from time to time for such
          changes.</string>
    <string name="terms_text_5">USER ACCOUNTS</string>
    <string name="terms_text_6">Account. If you create a user account for the Sites, you agree to complete the registration process by
          providing current, complete, and accurate information as required by Pointube. You are responsible for all
          activities that occur under your account. You agree to notify Pointube immediately of any unauthorized use
          of your account or any other breach of security. Pointube will not be liable for any loss that you may incur
          as a result of someone else using your account, either with or without your knowledge. In addition, you may
          be held liable for any losses incurred by Pointube or another party due to someone else using your account.
          You may not use anyone else\'s account at any time.</string>
    <string name="terms_text_7">PRIVACY NOTICE</string>
    <string name="terms_text_8">A copy of Pointube Privacy Policy that applies to the collection, use, disclosure and other processing of
          personal information by Pointube is posted on the Sites. These Terms of Service incorporate the entirety of
          the Pointube Privacy Policy. You consent to any personal information we may obtain about you (either via the
          Pointube Sites, by email, telephone, or any other means) being collected, stored and otherwise processed in
          accordance with the terms of the Privacy Policy.</string>
    <string name="terms_text_9">SITE CONTENT</string>
    <string name="terms_text_10">The Sites, including without limitation the text, graphics, photographs, software, video and audio content,
          and the like that appear on the website or mobile site (the "Site Content"), is owned by or licensed to
          Pointube, and is subject to copyright and other intellectual property rights under Thai Laws. Users may not
          re-post, republish, reproduce or copy the Site Content to other web sites, mobile applications, or
          otherwise, without the prior written consent of Pointube. Users cannot sell, or distribute, Site Content to
          third parties, prepare derivative works of or otherwise exploit Content without the prior written permission
          of Pointube. To request permission to re-post, republish, reproduce, copy, sell, distribute, prepare
          derivative works of or otherwise exploit Site Content, please submit your request in writing via
          service@pointube.com. Pointube has no obligation to grant you permission to re-post, republish, reproduce,
          copy, sell, distribute, prepare derivative works of or otherwise exploit Site Content. All of the Pointube
          trademarks, service marks and logos are owned by or licensed to Pointube and may not be used for any purpose
          without the prior written consent of Pointube.</string>
    <string name="terms_text_11">PERMITTED USES</string>
    <string name="terms_text_12">You agree not to use the Sites in any manner that could damage, disable, overburden, or impair any server,
          or the network(s) connected to any Pointube\' server, or interfere with any other party\'s use and enjoyment
          of the Sites. You may not attempt to gain unauthorized access to any portion of the Sites, other accounts,
          computer systems, or networks connected to any Pointube\' server, through hacking, password or data mining,
          or any other means. You may not obtain or attempt to obtain any materials or information through any means
          not intentionally made available to you on the Sites. You will not link to any part of the Sites if such
          activity is illegal, will cause damage to, or will otherwise harm Pointube or any other party. Moreover,
          Pointube reserves the right in its sole discretion to disable or otherwise terminate your use of the Sites,
          or any links you make to the Sites, or request you to do the same. Pointube reserves all of its rights in
          the Pointube Sites not expressly granted to you by these Terms of Service.</string>
    <string name="terms_text_13">REDEMPTIONS POLICY</string>
    <string name="terms_text_14">Pointube promotes the point and mile offers to you but does not guarantee the redemptions provided by the
          partner loyalty program operators. Pointube is not responsible for the service, eligibility, or termination
          of the offers.</string>
    <string name="terms_text_15">CLAIM OF COPYRIGHT INFRINGEMENT</string>
    <string name="terms_text_16">Pointube respects the intellectual property of others. If you believe in good faith that any Site Content,
          or other matter posted on the Sites infringes the copyright in a work you own, please contact, with
          correspondence containing the following:</string>
    <string name="terms_text_17">A physical signature of the owner, or a person authorized to act on behalf of the owner, of the copyright
          that is allegedly infringed; Identification of the copyrighted work allegedly infringed;</string>
    <string name="terms_text_18">Identifying information reasonably sufficient to allow determination by Pointube of the location of the
          material that is allegedly infringing; Information reasonably sufficient to permit Pointube to contact
          you;</string>
    <string name="terms_text_19">A statement that you have a good faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not
          authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law; and</string>
    <string name="terms_text_20">A statement that the information in the notification is accurate, and under penalty of perjury, that you
          are authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.</string>
    <string name="terms_text_21">You acknowledge that if you fail to comply with all of the requirements of this Section, your DMCA notice
          may not be valid. For any questions regarding this procedure, or to submit a complaint, please contact
          Pointube via service@pointube.com.</string>
    <string name="terms_text_22">LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES/ MOBILE SITES</string>
    <string name="terms_text_23">The Sites may contain advertisements and/or links to other sites ("Third Party Sites"). These links are
          provided solely for the convenience of the users. Pointube does not endorse, sanction or verify the accuracy
          or ownership of the information contained in the advertisements or the content of any Third Party Sites or
          any products or services advertised on Third Party Sites. If you decide to leave the Sites and navigate to
          Third Party Sites, or install any applications, software or download content from any such websites or
          mobile sites, you do so at your own risk. Once you access a Third Party Site through a link on the Pointube
          Sites, you may no longer be protected by these Terms of Service and you may be subject to the terms of
          service and other conditions of such Third Party Sites. You should review the applicable terms and policies,
          including privacy and data gathering practices, of any such site to which you navigate to from the Pointube
          Sites, or relating to any applications you use or install from such Third Party Sites. Concerns regarding a
          Third Party Site should be directed to the Third Party Site itself. Pointube bears no responsibility for any
          action associated with any Third Party Site. Moreover, Pointube does not imply an affiliation with any Third
          Party Site.</string>
    <string name="terms_text_24">LIMITATION OF LIABILITY</string>
    <string name="terms_text_25">You agree Pointube will not be held liable for any loss or damage incurred as a result of use of the Sites
          or services. You understand Pointube is not the seller of the goods or services advertised on the Sites.
          Pointube is a service provider and data handler for partner loyalty program operators. Pointube is not the
          agent of any partner loyalty program operators and takes no responsibility for the services or products for
          which partner loyalty program operators provide. Pointube has the right at any time to change, modify,
          correct, add to, discontinue, or retire any aspect or feature of the Sites, including, but not limited to,
          hours of availability, equipment needed for access or use, or the availability of the Sites (or any part
          thereof) on any particular device or communications service. Pointube has no obligation to provide you with
          notice of any such changes, and Pointube is under no obligation to provide you with any support, error
          corrections, updates, upgrades, bug fixes, and/or enhancements of the Sites.</string>
    <string name="terms_text_26">INDEMNIFICATION</string>
    <string name="terms_text_27">You agree to defend, indemnify, and hold harmless Pointube from all liabilities, claims, damages, losses,
          and expenses, including attorneys\' fees that arise from your use of the Sites. Pointube reserves the right,
          at its own expense, to assume the exclusive defense and control of any matter otherwise subject to
          indemnification by you, in which event you will cooperate with Pointube in asserting any available defenses.</string>
    <string name="terms_text_28">ARBITRATION AND JURISDICTION</string>
    <string name="terms_text_29">All disputes arising out of, relating to or connected with these Terms of Service, Privacy Policy, or your
          use of any part of the Pointube Sites, shall be referred to and finally resolved by arbitration under the
          Thai law. All disputes in arbitration will be handled solely between the named parties, and not on any
          representative of class basis. Notwithstanding any other provision of these Terms of Service, to the extent
          that you have in any manner violated or threatened to violate Pointube\'s intellectual property rights,
          Pointube reserves the right to seek injunctive or other appropriate relief in any court in Thailand, and you
          consent to exclusive jurisdiction and venue in such courts.</string>

    <string name="terms_accept_term">Accept Terms &amp; Conditions</string>
    <string name="terms_btn_next">Next</string>

    <!-- Register Phone -->
    <string name="register_text_phone_info"> Pleases input your mobile phone number In field below
            Verification code will be sent  via SMS to your mobile phone.</string>

    <string name="register_phone_toast_save_success">Save phone number successfully</string>
    <string name="register_phone_dialog_progress_saving_phone">Saving phone number…</string>

    <string name="register_phone_telephone_number">Telephone Number</string>
    <string name="register_phone_send_otp">Send OTP</string>

    <!-- Register OTP -->
    <string name="otp_text_info_1">Verification code has been sent to your mobile phone</string>
    <string name="otp_text_info_2">Please input the 6 digit in the field below</string>

    <string name="otp_toast_verify_successful">Verify OTP successfully</string>
    <string name="otp_dialog_progress_verifying">Verify OTP...</string>

    <string name="otp_text_verify_otp">Verify OTP</string>
    <string name="otp_text_verify">Verify</string>


    <!-- Brand Member -->
    <string name="brand_member_info_1">Please select the Brand(s) you want to view into the POINTUBE wallet</string>
    <string name="brand_member_select_all_title">Qualified Brands</string>
    <string name="brand_member_select_all_info">Brand that you have registered</string>
    <string name="brand_member_select_all_button">Select all</string>
    <string name="brand_member_select_hint">*For any question on above member data, please contact your reward program provider\'s callcenter for details.</string>

    <string name="brand_member_button_start">Next</string>

    <!-- Brand Non Member -->
    <string name="brand_non_member_info_1">Do you wish to become a member of these brand? \n If \'yes\', please select the brands from the list</string>
    <string name="brand_non_member_select_all_title">Register</string>
    <string name="brand_non_member_button_start">Let\'s start</string>

    <!-- Point -->
    <string name="point_text_title">POINTUBE Wallet</string>
    <string name="point_dialog_progress_selected_brand_content">Loading selected brand..</string>
    <string name="point_title">Outstanding Points</string>
    <string name="point_empty_state">To create your point wallet,\n please select at least 1 brand from the list</string>
    <string name="point_recommend_me_error">Please select at least 1 brand from the list to view recommend promotion.</string>
    <string name="point_info_helper">*For any questions on above points/miles data, please contact your reward program provider\'s call center for details.</string>

    <!-- About -->
    <string name="about_what_is_pointube">What is Pointube?</string>
    <string name="about_who_should_use">Who should use Pointube?</string>
    <string name="about_how_to_use">How to use Pointube?</string>
    <string name="about_faq">FAQ</string>
    <string name="about_contact_us">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="about_privacy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="about_terms_of_use">Terms of Use</string>
    <string name="about_text_title">About Pointube</string>

    <!-- Login -->
    <string name="login_dialog_login_title">Reset Password</string>
    <string name="login_dialog_login_positive">Reset</string>

    <string name="login_dialog_validate_pin_title">Validate Pin</string>
    <string name="login_dialog_validate_pin_positive">Validate</string>

    <string name="login_dialog_forgot_password_title">Forgot Password</string>

    <string name="login_dialog_progress_validate_forgot_password">Validate your email…</string>
    <string name="login_dialog_progress_resetting_password">Resetting password…</string>
    <string name="login_dialog_progress_login">Logging in…</string>
    <string name="login_dialog_progress_request_otp">Request Otp…</string>
    <string name="login_dialog_forgot_password_otp_hint">Please input the 4 digit in the field below</string>
    <string name="login_dialog_forget_password_positive">Change</string>

    <string name="login_toast_login_success">Login success</string>
    <string name="login_toast_forgot_success">Reset password success</string>

    <string name="login_text_email">Email</string>
    <string name="login_text_password">Password</string>
    <string name="login_text_remember_me">Remember Me</string>
    <string name="login_text_sign_up">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="login_text_login">Log in</string>
    <string name="login_text_new_user">New User?</string>
    <string name="login_text_forget_password">Forget Password</string>

    <!-- Setting -->
    <string name="setting_text_dialog_progress_logging_out">Logging out…</string>
    <string name="setting_text_my_profile">My Profile</string>
    <string name="setting_text_my_brand">My Brands</string>
    <string name="setting_text_logout">Log out</string>
    <string name="setting_text_title">Setting</string>

    <!-- My Brand -->
    <string name="my_brand_text_title">My Brands</string>

    <!-- My Profile -->
    <string name="my_profile_text_title">My Profile</string>

    <string name="my_profile_dialog_change_password_hint_old_password">Old Password</string>
    <string name="my_profile_dialog_change_password_hint_new_password">New Password</string>
    <string name="my_profile_dialog_change_password_hint_repeat_new_password">Repeat New Password</string>

    <string name="my_profile_dialog_change_password_title">Change Password</string>
    <string name="my_profile_toast_change_password_success">Change password success</string>

    <string name="my_profile_dialog_progress_update_profile_content">Updating profile…</string>
    <string name="my_profile_toast_update_profile_success">Update profile successful</string>

    <string name="my_profile_btn_save">Save</string>

    <!-- Brand Non Member -->
    <string name="brand_non_member_toast_save_successful">Save brand successful</string>
    <string name="brand_non_member_toast_save_failed">Save brand failed</string>
    <string name="brand_non_member_toast_empty_brand">Empty brand</string>
    <string name="brand_non_member_toast_loading_error">Loading brand error</string>

    <string name="brand_non_member_dialog_progress_save_brand">Saving brand…</string>

    <string name="brand_non_member_btn_select_all">Select all</string>
    <string name="brand_non_member_btn_un_select_all">Unselect all</string>

    <!-- Home -->
    <string name="home_toast_empty_program_list">Empty Programs</string>
    <string name="home_text_reward_program">Reward Programs</string>
    <string name="home_btn_login">Login</string>
    <string name="home_text_new_user">New User?</string>
    <string name="home_text_sign_up">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="home_text_title">Home</string>


    <!-- Promotion Detail -->
    <string name="promotion_detail_text_start">Start</string>
    <string name="promotion_detail_text_point">Point</string>
    <string name="promotion_detail_text_special_point">Special Point</string>
    <string name="promotion_detail_text_time">Time</string>
    <string name="promotion_detail_text_place">Place</string>
    <string name="promotion_detail_text_url">Url</string>
    <string name="promotion_detail_text_promotion_period">Promotion Period</string>
    <string name="promotion_detail_text_channel">Channels</string>
    <string name="promotion_detail_text_how_to_redeem">How To Redeem</string>
    <string name="promotion_detail_text_term_and_condition">Terms and Conditions</string>

    <string name="promotion_detail_text_1_day">1 day left</string>
    <string name="promotion_detail_text_more_than_1_day">days left</string>
    <string name="promotion_detail_text_less_than_1_day">In 24 hours</string>

    <!-- Promotion List -->
    <string name="promotion_list_loading_program">Loading program list…</string>
    <string name="promotion_list_empty_loading_program">Promotion is coming…</string>
    <string name="promotion_list_text_title">Promotion</string>

    <string name="promotion_list_text_recommend_me_error">Please select at least 1 brand from the list to view recommend promotion.</string>

    <string name="promotion_list_text_hot_deal">Hot deal</string>
    <string name="promotion_list_text_dining">Dining</string>
    <string name="promotion_list_text_shopping">Shopping</string>
    <string name="promotion_list_text_travel">Travel</string>
    <string name="promotion_list_text_entertainment">Entertainment</string>
    <string name="promotion_list_text_health">Health</string>
    <string name="promotion_list_text_beauty">Beauty</string>
    <string name="promotion_list_text_education">Education</string>
    <string name="promotion_list_text_reading">Reading</string>
    <string name="promotion_list_text_home_and_living">Home and Living</string>
    <string name="promotion_list_text_it_gadget">IT Gadget</string>
    <string name="promotion_list_text_other">Other</string>

    <!-- Program List -->
    <string name="program_list_text_login_to_see_more">Please login to see more promotion</string>

    <!-- Recommend Me -->
    <string name="recommend_me_title">Search by brands</string>

    <!-- Chart Detail -->
    <string name="chart_detail_text_round_trip">Round Trip</string>
    <string name="chart_detail_text_one_way_trip">One way Trip</string>

    <string name="chart_detail_text_economy_class">Economy Class</string>
    <string name="chart_detail_text_premium_economy_class">Premium Economy Class</string>
    <string name="chart_detail_text_royal_silk_class">Royal Silk Class</string>
    <string name="chart_detail_text_royal_first_class">Royal First Class</string>

    <!-- Thai Airline -->
    <string name="thai_airline_title">Air award chart</string>

    <!-- Zone 2-->
    <!-- Utility -->

    <!-- Error message -->
    <string name="error_msg_internet_connection">Problem with internet connection or server, please try again</string>

    <!-- Register Form Validation -->
    <string name="validate_email">Invalid email</string>
    <string name="validate_password">Password must be at least 4 characters</string>
    <string name="validate_repeat_password">Repeat password is not match with password</string>
    <string name="validate_first_name">First name must not be empty</string>
    <string name="validate_last_name">Last name must not be empty</string>
    <string name="validate_validate_citizen_id">CitizenID must be 13 characters</string>
    <string name="validate_passport">Passport must be at least 10 characters</string>

    <!-- Dialog Default Value -->
    <string name="dialog_default_ok">OK</string>
    <string name="dialog_default_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="dialog_default_progress_loading_title">Please wait</string>

    <!-- Promotion list view group -->
    <string name="viewgroup_promotion_list_points">Points</string>
    <string name="viewgroup_promotion_list_read_more">Read more…</string>

</resources>

